<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest News | Robot Mirroring Research Group</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Latest News</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Latest News</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at ACII2021</title>
      <link>/post/21-10-01-aciiw-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-10-01-aciiw-presentation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our paper on Robot mirroring: Improving well-being by fostering empathy with an artificial agent representing the self was presented at ACII2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We searched the literature to find supporting or opposing evidence for the robot mirroring framework. The results showed an increasing interest in self-tracking technologies for well-being management. Current discussions disseminate what can be achieved with different levels of automation; the type and relevance of feedback; and the role that artificial agents, such as chatbots and robots, might play to support people&amp;rsquo;s therapies. These findings support further development of the robot mirroring framework to improve medical, hedonic, and eudaemonic well-being.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at ROMAN2020</title>
      <link>/post/20-09-30-roman20_presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/20-09-30-roman20_presentation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our paper on Robot mirroring: Promoting Empathy with an Artificial Agent by Reflecting the User&amp;rsquo;s Physiological Affective States was presented at ROMAN2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the dire situation in Italy due to COVID, ROMAN organizers did a wonderful job to pivot the conference to an online event. We presented our work and obtained great feedback!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
